

Jovita Morkūnė Quality Improvement Specialist

+370 636 58227 jovita.morkune@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/jovita-morkune/ Kaunas, Lithuania

EXPERIENCE

Quality Improvement Specialist R1 RCM

03/2016 - 02/2020

- Ensured the high-quality work of my team specialists.
- Improved several processes with macro commands to work processes in a more effective way and to avoid repetitive errors.
- Initiated additional projects with other teams, which helped to generate more income for the company.
- Investigated many trends and issues related to rejected claims, in order to resolve it faster and prevent more rejections.

Account Resolution Specialist Intermedix

05/2015 - 03/2016

- Identified reasons for denied insurance claims and effectively resolved them by determining a course of action in the revenue cycle management system.
- Maintained high productivity and work quality results.
- Worked on various projects, collaborated with team members to reach the team goals.

EDUCATION

International Business Kaunas University of Technology 2018 Master's degree

Finance

Kaunas University of Technology 2015 Bachelor's degree

CERTIFICATES

The Web Developer Bootcamp (Udemy)

02/2020 - Present

Global Collaboration Certificate (X-Culture)

12/2017 - Present

SUMMARY

I am responsible, diligent, attentive and have good interpersonal skills. I am used to an agile work environment and can quickly adapt to changing business requirements.

Over the past 4 years, I had an opportunity to work with culturally diverse teams, where I was focusing on ensuring a high level of quality in the work my team was doing.

Currently, I'm studying a lot to become a software QA engineer. I would love to join a software company where I could create value by contributing to the quality assurance of interesting software products while also gaining more practical experience.

SKILLS

Teamwork Expert

Quality Assurance Advanced

Analytical Skills Advanced

JIRA Intermediate

JavaScript Beginner

HTML/CSS Beginner

MongoDB Beginner

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate

Russian Basic
Lithuanian Native